<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ziabs.com/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://ziabs.com/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-05-30T23:50:58+05:30</updated><id>https://ziabs.com/blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ziAbs</title><author><name>Tracy</name></author><entry><title type="html">The Shiva Trilogy</title><link href="https://ziabs.com/blog/2020/shiva-trilogy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Shiva Trilogy" /><published>2020-05-30T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-30T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>https://ziabs.com/blog/2020/shiva-trilogy</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ziabs.com/blog/2020/shiva-trilogy.html">&lt;div class=&quot;ziabs-notes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.in/gp/product/B00DJLRTEM/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=3638&amp;amp;creative=24630&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B00DJLRTEM&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=ziabs-21&amp;amp;linkId=68c740af0e70ce8b519e89dcb94f1d37&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/51V5kOB32qL._SL250_.jpg&quot; data-aos=&quot;flip-left&quot; data-aos-duration=&quot;1500&quot; class=&quot;float-left mr-3&quot; alt=&quot;The Shiva Trilogy&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;media-body&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.in/gp/product/B00DJLRTEM/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=3638&amp;amp;creative=24630&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B00DJLRTEM&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=ziabs-21&amp;amp;linkId=68c740af0e70ce8b519e89dcb94f1d37&quot;&gt;The Shiva Trilogy is the collection the best selling books,
  The Immortals of Meluha , The Secert of the Nagas and The Oath Of the Vayuputras written by Amish.The Immortals of Meluha -1900 BC. In what modern Indians mistakenly call the Indus Valley Civilisation.
  The Immortals of Meluha -1900 BC. In what modern Indians mistakenly call the Indus Valley Civilisation. The inhabitants of that period called it the land of Meluha – a near perfect empire created many centuries earlier by Lord Ram, one of the greatest monarchs that ever lived. This once proud empire and its Suryavanshi rulers face severe perils as its primary river, the revered Saraswati, is slowly drying to extinction. They also face devastating terrorist attacks from the east, the land of the Chandravanshis. To make matters worse, the Chandravanshis appear to have allied with the Nagas, an ostracised and sinister race of deformed humans with astonishing martial skills. The only hope for the Suryavanshis is an ancient legend: ‘When evil reaches epic proportions, when all seems lost, when it appears that your enemies have triumphed, a hero will emerge.’ Is the rough-hewn Tibetan immigrant Shiva, really that hero? And does he want to be that hero at all? Drawn suddenly to his destiny, by duty as well as by love, will Shiva lead the Suryavanshi vengeance and destroy evil? the simple man whose karma re-cast him as our Mahadev, the God of Gods Today . The Secert of the Nagas -He is a God.4000 years ago, He was just a man.The hunt is on. The sinister Naga warrior has killed his friend Brahaspati and now stalks his wife Sati. Shiva, the Tibetan immigrant who is the prophesied destroyer of evil, will not rest till he finds his demonic adversary. His vengeance and the path to evil will lead him to the door of the Nagas, the serpent people. Of that he is certain.The evidence of the malevolent rise of evil is everywhere. A kingdom is dying as it is held to ransom for a miracle drug. A crown prince is murdered. The Vasudevs – Shiva’s philosopher guides – betray his unquestioning faith as they take the aid of the dark side. Even the perfect empire, Meluha is riddled with a terrible secret in Maika, the city of births. Unknown to Shiva, a master puppeteer is playing a grand game. In a journey that will take him across the length and breadth of ancient India, Shiva searches for the truth in a land of deadly mysteries – only to find that nothing is what it seems.Fierce battles will be fought. Surprising alliances will be forged. Unbelievable secrets will be revealed .The Oath Of the Vayuputras -Shiva is gathering his forces. He reaches the Naga capital,Panchavati, and Evil is finally revealed. The Neelkanth prepares for a holy war against his true enemy, a man whose name instils dread in the fiercest of warriors. India convulses under the onslaught of a series of brutal battles. It's a war for the very soul of the nation. Many will die. But Shiva must not fail, no matter what the cost. In his desperation, he reaches out to the ones who have never offered any help to him: the Vayuputras.Will he succeed? And what will be the real cost of battling Evil? To India? And to Shiva's soul? Discover the answer to these mysteries in this bestselling Shiva Trilogy.
  &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Tracy</name></author><summary type="html">The Shiva Trilogy is the collection the best selling books, The Immortals of Meluha , The Secert of the Nagas and The Oath Of the Vayuputras written by Amish.The Immortals of Meluha -1900 BC. In what modern Indians mistakenly call the Indus Valley Civilisation. The Immortals of Meluha -1900 BC. In what modern Indians mistakenly call the Indus Valley Civilisation. The inhabitants of that period called it the land of Meluha – a near perfect empire created many centuries earlier by Lord Ram, one of the greatest monarchs that ever lived. This once proud empire and its Suryavanshi rulers face severe perils as its primary river, the revered Saraswati, is slowly drying to extinction. They also face devastating terrorist attacks from the east, the land of the Chandravanshis. To make matters worse, the Chandravanshis appear to have allied with the Nagas, an ostracised and sinister race of deformed humans with astonishing martial skills. The only hope for the Suryavanshis is an ancient legend: ‘When evil reaches epic proportions, when all seems lost, when it appears that your enemies have triumphed, a hero will emerge.’ Is the rough-hewn Tibetan immigrant Shiva, really that hero? And does he want to be that hero at all? Drawn suddenly to his destiny, by duty as well as by love, will Shiva lead the Suryavanshi vengeance and destroy evil? the simple man whose karma re-cast him as our Mahadev, the God of Gods Today . The Secert of the Nagas -He is a God.4000 years ago, He was just a man.The hunt is on. The sinister Naga warrior has killed his friend Brahaspati and now stalks his wife Sati. Shiva, the Tibetan immigrant who is the prophesied destroyer of evil, will not rest till he finds his demonic adversary. His vengeance and the path to evil will lead him to the door of the Nagas, the serpent people. Of that he is certain.The evidence of the malevolent rise of evil is everywhere. A kingdom is dying as it is held to ransom for a miracle drug. A crown prince is murdered. The Vasudevs – Shiva’s philosopher guides – betray his unquestioning faith as they take the aid of the dark side. Even the perfect empire, Meluha is riddled with a terrible secret in Maika, the city of births. Unknown to Shiva, a master puppeteer is playing a grand game. In a journey that will take him across the length and breadth of ancient India, Shiva searches for the truth in a land of deadly mysteries – only to find that nothing is what it seems.Fierce battles will be fought. Surprising alliances will be forged. Unbelievable secrets will be revealed .The Oath Of the Vayuputras -Shiva is gathering his forces. He reaches the Naga capital,Panchavati, and Evil is finally revealed. The Neelkanth prepares for a holy war against his true enemy, a man whose name instils dread in the fiercest of warriors. India convulses under the onslaught of a series of brutal battles. It's a war for the very soul of the nation. Many will die. But Shiva must not fail, no matter what the cost. In his desperation, he reaches out to the ones who have never offered any help to him: the Vayuputras.Will he succeed? And what will be the real cost of battling Evil? To India? And to Shiva's soul? Discover the answer to these mysteries in this bestselling Shiva Trilogy.</summary></entry></feed>